Jane Aitken Papers 1784-1814 Mss.B.Ai9
American Philosophical Society
- Jane Aitken Papers (Box 1)
  - Accounts, n.d.; 3 items; Vaughan, John